Richard Burk A. Orofeo I Software Developer

+63966 411 4873

Works: 1 https://github.com/rbo13

Residence

Cebu City, Philippines

Homepage

rbo13

Email

rborofeo@gmail.com

Go	++++	NodeJS	++++	JavaScript ++++	GraphQL	+++	Python	+++	MySQL	++++
Git	++++	Docker	+++	Kubernetes +++	AWS	+++	GCP	+++	CI/CD	+++

A highly focused software developer with experience in a variety of development and engineering positions. Well-versed in technology and writing code to create systems that are reliable and user-friendly. Innovative creator to develop software that is customized to meet a company's organizational needs, highlight their core competencies, and further their success.

Work Experience:

Senior Software Engineer at A-FIS Lab Ph. Inc

August 2018 - Present

Lead a small team of developers to work with our In-house, and Client Projects. We design and develop scalable backend architecture. Also, I am the point of contact in regards with our technical specifications. Configures our CI/CD pipeline for the deployment of our web applications using AWS running on ECS.

Junior Software Engineer at A-FIS Lab Ph. Inc

August 2017 - August 2018

Applied clean code practices and design patterns to develop readable, maintainable and scalable code for a web application. Improved existing code using SOLID design principles. Worked on creating a reusable internal library for our different projects.

```
Go MySQL Docker JavaScript ReactJS
```

Junior Software Developer at Coderepubliq

June 2016 - Jan 2017

Works as a backend developer. I design and develop RESTful APIs with NodeJS. Assisted mobile and frontend teams in solving different issues.

```
JavaScript NodeJS AngularJS MEAN
```

Education:

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Universion of Cebu - Main Campus [June 2012 - March 2016]

Additional experience:

Freelance Developer

Works as a remote backend developer using NodeJS. Also, created a tweet bot to aggregate news from different sources. Maintains performance of existing client websites.

